Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/ceciliah-3bb0bb9 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Spanish Italian

Teaching

Languages

English (Professional Working)
Spanish (Native or Bilingual)
Italian (Full Professional)

Certifications

Certified Medical Surgical Registered Nurse (CMSRN) CPR for Helathcare Providers Certified Nursing Assitant I Certified Nursing Assistant II

Honors-Awards

Sigma Kappa Delta membership

Phi Theta Kappa Honor Society membership

National Society of Leadership and Success membership

2015 AORN Coastal Chapter 3405 Nursing Student Scholarship

Cecilia Habra

RN, CMSRN, Trilingual Medical Case Manger United States

Summary

I graduated from the Associate Degree in Nursing Program on May 8, 2015 with honors, Phi Thetta Kappa, and Sigma Kappa Delta Honor societies. My GPA is 3.629/4. I am a 2015 Association of PeriOperative Registered Nurses (AORN) Coastal Chapter 3405 Student Nurse Scholarship's recipient, and I am currently member of the MSNBC. As a student, I served as Team Leader for my clinical group in the Progressive Care Unit at Carteret General Hospital. With my clinical group, I worked and presented a QI project that was chosen to be presented in the State's Nurse's instructor's convention, and is implemented currently at Carteret Health Care per protocol. I am a member of the MSNCB, the National Society of Leadership and Success, the Phi Theta Kappa Honor Society, and the Sigma Kappa Delta English Honor Society. I am trilingual-English, Spanish, Italian. Besides Nursing, I have a background in Speech Therapy, Language Pathology, Audiology, Early Stimulation, and Teaching. In my job at CHC I administered patient care in an effective, timely manner; accurately performed tasks and treatments in accordance with established policies, and procedures and the listing guidelines for RN, and effectively interacted and communicated with patients and families and other health care team members. I was part of the Pressure Ulcer Surveillance Team and the Journal Club. I obtained the Medical - Surgical Nursing Certification by the Medical-Surgical Nursing Certification Board. I left CHC after more than 5 years to pursue my dreams of applying my skills and knowledge to reaching and helping a more diverse community, and joined the Southern Rehabilitation Network, Inc. company as Bilingual Medical Case Manager.

Experience

Southern Rehab Network
Bilingual Medical Case Manager
May 2018 - Present (2 years 3 months)

Raleigh, North Carolina

Carteret Health Care

5 years 8 months

Staff RN

July 2015 - August 2018 (3 years 2 months)

Morehead City, North Carolina

RN, CMSRN

Certified Nurse Aide II

January 2013 - June 2015 (2 years 6 months)

Morehead City, North Carolina

- Administer daily patient care in an effective, timely manner
- Accurately perform tasks and treatments in accordance with established policies, and procedures and the listing guidelines for CNA II
- Effectively interact and communicate with patients and families and other health care team members

Escuela Especial Nro. 240 "Dr. Ramon Carrillo" Fonoaudióloga

March 1994 - January 2003 (8 years 11 months)

Santiago del Estero, Argentina

Speech Therapist and Language Pathologist for Children with Special Needs

Insituto "Dante Alighieri" Italian Teacher 1999 - 2002 (3 years) San Luis, Argentina

Italian Teacher

IPAL

Instituto de Psicologia, Audiología y Lenguaje 1989 - 1998 (9 years)

Santiago del Estero, Argentina

Speech Therapist and Language Patholigist for Children and Adults at IPAL--Interdisciplinary Clinic for Neurology, Speech Therapy, Language Pathology, Audiology, Psicology, Physical Therapy, Occupational Therapy, Musical Therapy, and Physical evaluation, diagnosis, treatment, rehabilitation and therapy.

CER Centro de Rehabilitación Fonoaudióloga

January 1993 - January 1997 (4 years 1 month)

Santiago del Estero, Argentina

Speech Therapist, Language Pathologist

Education

Carteret Community College

Associate's degree, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (2013 - 2015)

Carteret Community College

Pre-Nursing Studies · (2012 - 2012)

Carteret Community College

Associate's degree, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (2011 - 2011)

Universidad Nacional de San Luis

Audiology/Audiologist and Speech-Language Pathology/

Pathologist · (2000 - 2002)

Dante Alighieri

Italian Language · (1991 - 1996)